A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4 FA457
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 1966, 1969-1973; 4; 13.2 Cubic Feet 11 record storage cartons.
  - Robert A. (Bob) Wands Photos
    - Contact Prints
      - 1970
        - 1970 September
          - General Reception - Grossingers, 1970 September 6 (Box 100)
          - Photo Session: Local Candidates - Garden City, 1970 September 8 (Box 100)
          - Narcotics Groups at 55th Street, 1970 September 8 (Box 100)
          - Labor Groups Pledge Support, 1970 September 8 (Box 100)
          - Rockefeller/Caso Headquarters - Garden City, 1970 September 8 (Box 100)
          - Civil Service Employees Association Drop-In & Annual Meeting - Buffalo, 1970 September 9 (Box 100)
          - Irondequoit Citizens Association, 1970 September 9 (Box 100)
          - Drug Abuse Meeting: Irondequoit, 1970 September 9 (Box 100)
          - Dedication: Hornell Airport, 1970 September 9 (Box 100)
          - Hornell Chamber of Commerce Dinner and Reception, 1970 September 9 (Box 100)
          - Dedication: Albany's NYS. Civil Service Building (New Wing) Ribbon Cutting/ Plaque Unveiling of Cleveland/Roosevelt History Room (Ersa Poston attended), 1970 September 10 (Box 100)
          - Headquarters Opening: Assemblyman Fred G. Fields - Albany, 1970 September 10 (Box 100)
          - Albany rotary Club Luncheon, 1970 September 10 (Box 100)
          - Statewide Meeting on Children & Youth and Reception for Youth Delegates, 1970 September 10 (Box 100)
          - Yonkers Republican City Committee Annual Dinner Dance, 1970 September 10 (Box 100)
          - Brooklyn Walking Tour, 1970 September 11 (Box 100)
          - Plaque Presentation /Mesivta Baer Shmuel, 1970 September 11 (Box 100)
          - San Gennaro Festival (lower Manhattan), 1970 September 11 (Box 100)
          - Endorsement: Francis Adams, 1970 September 11 (Box 100)
          - TWA Hi-Jack Family meets Governor, 1970 September 11 (Box 100)
          - National Drug Conference - Washington DC, 1970 September 12 (Box 100)
          - Endorsement: Ario Procaccino, 1970 September 14 (Box 100)
          - New York Publishers Association Luncheon - Albany, 1970 September 14 (Box 100)
          - 100 Black Men, Inc.- Dinner (NY City), 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Headquarters Visit: "Friends of Rockefeller Team" - Albany, 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Tour of Cluett-Peabody Plant - Troy, 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Meeting with Alton Sliter, Editor & Publisher of "Troy Record", 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Ewald Nyquist Inauguration as NYS. Commissioner of Education - Saratoga, 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Foreign Language Press Reception - Sardis, 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Richard Schwartz Testimonial Dinner - Garment Center, 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Dinner Honoring Mr/Mrs Charles Goodell, 1970 September 15 (Box 100)
          - Port of Albany dinner Reception - Albany, 1970 September 16 (Box 100)
          - Suffolk County P.B.A. Board of Governors Informal Lunch - Deer Park, 1970 September 16 (Box 100)
          - Dedication: First Hostel for Retarded Young Adults - Brooklyn, 1970 September 16 (Box 100)
          - Drug Abuse Meeting: Garden City, 1970 September 16 (Box 100)
          - Headquarters Opening: "Independents for Rockefeller" - Fulton, 1970 September 17 (Box 100)
          - Drug Abuse Meeting: Liverpool, 1970 September 17 (Box 100)
          - Public Reception - Owego, 1970 September 17 (Box 100)
          - Opening of General Pulaski's Day - Pulaski, 1970 September 17 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Builders Association, 1970 September 18 (Box 100)
          - Westchester Advertising Club Luncheon - Scarsdale, 1970 September 18 (Box 100)
          - Republican State Committee Women's Finance Division Luncheon - New York, 1970 September 18 (Box 100)
          - Foreign Press conference - Pocantico Hills, 1970 September 18 (Box 100)
          - Governors Club - Pocantico Hills, 1970 September 18 (Box 100)
          - Bay Ridge Walking Tour - Brooklyn, 1970 September 19 (Box 100)
          - Storefront Opening: Brooklyn, 1970 September 19 (Box 100)
          - Parade: Stuben Day Parade along 5th Avenue, 1970 September 19 (Box 100)
          - Green County Republican Committee Dinner - Hunter, 1970 September 19 (Box 100)
          - Baseball Game: "Rocky's Team" vs. cast of "Hair" - Central Park, 1970 September 20 (Box 100)
          - United Jewish Appeal Dinner, honoring Golda Meir - Hilton, 1970 September 20 (Box 100)
          - Westchester Arts Council Reception - Katonah, 1970 September 20 (Box 100)
          - Memorial Art Gallery Reception - Rochester, 1970 September 21 (Box 100)
          - Upstate Campaign Kick-Off Rally - Flagship, 1970 September 21 (Box 100)
          - Monroe County Republican Finance Committee Reception - Flagship, 1970 September 21 (Box 100)
          - Batavia Highway Breakfast, 1970 September 22 (Box 100)
          - Tour of Sylvania Plant - Batavia, 1970 September 22 (Box 100)
          - Orleans Champagne Buffet, 1970 September 22 (Box 100)
          - Niagara County College Groundbreaking, 1970 September 22 (Box 100)
          - Senator Brydges Testimonial Dinner, 1970 September 22 (Box 100)
          - Visit w/Building and Construction Tradesmen - World Trade Center, Manhattan, 1970 September 23 (Box 100)
          - John Marchi Testimonial Dinner - Staten Island, 1970 September 23 (Box 100)
          - Uniformed Fire Officers Association Meeting - Hotel New Yorker, 1970 September 23 (Box 100)
          - Sanitation Men/ Endorse Governor (John Delury, etc.), 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - Annual Convention of NYS. Conference of International Union of Operating Engineers - Endorse Governor (Commodore), 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Association of Barbers Endorse Governor - St. Regis Hotel, 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - Propeller Club Luncheon - Commodore, 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - Governor Meets Sophia Loren, 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - Long Island Press/Annual Distinguished Service Award Dinner - Garden City, 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - Affiliated Young Democrats, Inc.- Hotel Picadilly - New York, 1970 September 24 (Box 100)
          - Beth Israel Methadone Treatment Center - Great Neck, 1970 September 25 (Box 100)
          - Dedication: Sanctuary & New School of Temple Beth-el, 1970 September 25 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Conservation Council 37th Annual Meeting - Monticello, 1970 September 25 (Box 100)
          - Dedication: Poughkeepsie Sewage Treatment Plant, 1970 September 25 (Box 100)
          - Puerto Rican Homeowners Banquet - Roosevelt, 1970 September 25 (Box 100)
          - Louis Laurino endorses Governor, 1970 September 28 (Box 100)
          - Jamestown Hotel - Coffee Reception, 1970 September 29 (Box 100)
          - Combined Service Club Luncheon - Dunkirk, 1970 September 29 (Box 100)
          - Kiamesha County Officers Association of NYS. Fall Banquet, 1970 September 29 (Box 100)
          - Sullivan County Republican Committee Dinner, 1970 September 29 (Box 100)
          - West Farms Neighborhood Housing Development Groundbreaking - Bronx, 1970 September 30 (Box 100)
          - Twin Park Construction Start - Bronx, 1970 September 30 (Box 100)
          - Sullivan County Republican Committee Dinner (from 9/29 file, picture runover), 1970 September 30 (Box 100)
          - Statewide Polish Reception, 1970 September 30 (Box 100)
        - 1970 October
          - Albany County Republican Committee Annual All-Star Gala - Albany, 1970 October 2 (Box 100)
          - Ten Eyck Development Demolition, 1970 October 2 (Box 100)
          - Office & Professional Employees International Union, Local 153, 1970 October 2 (Box 100)
          - American Legion Dinner - Waldorf, 1970 October 2 (Box 100)
          - Community Mayors - Man of the Year Award, 1970 October 2 (Box 100)
          - 1970 October 3 (Box 100)
          - Pulaski Day Parade - NY City, 1970 October 4 (Box 100)
          - Woman's Rally for Rockefeller/Caso - Nassau County, 1970 October 4 (Box 100)
          - Nassau County Press Association Annual "Grass Roots" Award Dinner, 1970 October 4 (Box 100)
          - Onondaga County Reception - Syracuse, 1970 October 5 (Box 100)
          - Gannet Newspaper Luncheon - Buffalo, 1970 October 5 (Box 100)
          - South Side Bowling Center - Buffalo, 1970 October 5 (Box 100)
          - WBEN-TV - "Contact" - Buffalo, 1970 October 6 (Box 100)
          - Great Lakes Commission Award, 1970 October 6 (Box 100)
          - Governors Environmental Forum -Hamburg, 1970 October 6 (Box 100)
          - Walking Tour - Fulton Street (NY City), 1970 October 7 (Box 100)
          - Headquarters Opening - Brooklyn, 1970 October 7 (Box 100)
          - Young Israel of Ocean Parkway Synagogue meeting with Rabbis, 1970 October 7 (Box 100)
          - Endorsement: Hotel & Hospital Workers - Royal Manhattan Hotel, 1970 October 7 (Box 100)
          - Richmond County Republican Committee fund - Raising Dinner -Staten Island, 1970 October 7 (Box 100)
          - Abba Eban visits Governor's 55th Street Office, 1970 October 8 (Box 100)
          - Manuel Ramos Endorses Governor, 1970 October 8 (Box 100)
          - School children tour Campaign Headquarters, 1970 October 8 (Box 100)
          - Wins Radio News Conference Taping (at Wins), 1970 October 9 (Box 100)
          - Queens Citizens Endorse Governor, 1970 October 9 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Fire Fighters make Governor Honorary Fire Chief, 1970 October 9 (Box 100)
          - Governor with delegation from Young Israel - Senator Books, 1970 October 9 (Box 100)
          - 1970 October 11 (Box 100)
          - Orthodox Jewish Leaders Breakfast, 1970 October 12 (Box 100)
          - Pulaski Day Parade (photos from 01011), 1970 October 12 (Box 100)
          - Avenue "D" walking Tour & Bella Abzug, 1970 October 12 (Box 100)
          - Cardinal Cooke Dinner, 1970 October 12 (Box 100)
          - Samuel Liebowitz Endorses Governor, 1970 October 12 (Box 100)
          - Columbus Day Parade, 1970 October 12 (Box 100)
          - Long Island Railroad Electrification Ceremony (Ronan), 1970 October 13 (Box 100)
          - Smithtown construction start of State Office Building & Suffolk County Office Tower, 1970 October 13 (Box 100)
          - Labor Management Reception Drop-In - Great Neck, 1970 October 13 (Box 100)
          - Great Neck Shopping Tour (Shop Center), 1970 October 13 (Box 100)
          - Nassau County Village Officials Association 45th Annual Dinner Mayor Driscoll, 1970 October 13 (Box 100)
          - Orange County Republican Committee Reception - Newburgh, 1970 October 14 (Box 100)
          - Stewart Air Field - Newburgh, 1970 October 14 (Box 100)
          - Rocky Marciano Lodge # 2226, 1970 October 14 (Box 100)
          - Alfred E. Smith Exhibit - Albany (showing Mrs. Emily Warner Smith), 1970 October 14 (Box 100)
          - South Mall Towers Site - Albany, 1970 October 14 (Box 100)
          - Meeting with Newburgh & Middletown Editors, 1970 October 14 (Box 100)
          - Sanitation Workers Association, Local 831, I.B.T. Shop Stewards Meeting 25 Cliff Street, 1970 October 15 (Box 100)
          - Mike Wallace Interview at 55th Street, 1970 October 15 (Box 100)
          - WOR/Martha Dean Radio Show (live) - NY City, 1970 October 15 (Box 100)
          - Spyros Skouras Ethnic Committee Dinner - Americana, 1970 October 15 (Box 100)
          - NYS. Medical society Cornerstone - Lake Success, 1970 October 15 (Box 100)
          - Governor Tours Campaign Headquarters - 575 Madison Ave, 1970 October 15 (Box 100)
          - Italian Endorsement & Breakfast with Visiting Mayors - Royal Manhattan, 1970 October 16 (Box 100)
          - Stewart Airfield to M.T.A. (from 10/14), 1970 October 16 (Box 100)
          - Sales Executive Club Luncheon - Waldorf, 1970 October 16 (Box 100)
          - Polish American Democratic Committee of Greater New York Banquet, 1970 October 16 (Box 100)
          - Hispanic Transit Society Dance - Park Sheraton, 1970 October 16 (Box 100)
          - Service Employees Joint Council #11 Cocktail Reception - Commodore, 1970 October 16 (Box 100)
          - Bronx Walking Tour, 1970 October 17 (Box 100)
          - Villa Bianca - Federation of Civic Council Convention, 1970 October 17 (Box 100)
          - Columbian Association Reception Drop-In - Lido Beach, 1970 October 17 (Box 100)
          - NBC "Searchlight", 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Puerto Rican TV Telethon, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Bronx Cadet Groundbreaking - NY City Mission Society -New Cadet Headquarters, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Electrical Welfare Club Breakfast, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Police Department Shomrim Society Spiritual Breakfast, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Van Nest Recreation Center, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Amendola Wedding w/Mario Procanccino Attending, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Governor at U.N. Delegation to 25th General Assembly Reception -Mayor Lindsay Attending, 1970 October 18 (Box 100)
          - Queens Democrats for Rockefeller Headquarters, 1970 October 19 (Box 100)
          - Flushing Walking Tour, 1970 October 19 (Box 100)
          - Narcotics Control Conference of NYS.- Rochester, 1970 October 19 (Box 100)
          - Governors Reception - U.N. 25th General Assembly, 1970 October 19 (Box 100)
          - 55th Street Rally/Following Lindsay's endorsement of Arthur Goldberg, 1970 October 20 (Box 100)
          - Women for Rockefeller Breakfast - Plaza, 1970 October 20 (Box 100)
          - Golda Meir Reception - Waldorf, 1970 October 20 (Box 100)
          - Lunch with Time, Inc. editors, 1970 October 20 (Box 100)
          - Governors Reception - U.N. (Lincoln Center) (photos from 10/19), 1970 October 21 (Box 100)
          - Association of Colleges & Universities of NYS. Annual Meeting Luncheon at Pace College (Lindsay is shown here also), 1970 October 21 (Box 100)
          - WNBC News Interview - Gabe Pressman & live TV, 1970 October 21 (Box 100)
          - Governor w/taxi drivers and union leaders outside 55th Street office, 1970 October 21 (Box 100)
          - Alfred E. Smith Memori Foundation Dinner, 25th Anniversary - Waldorf, 1970 October 21 (Box 100)
          - Meeting with editors of El Diario - 181 Hudson Street, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - General Foods Corporation - White Plains, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - Railroad Grade Crossing Elimination - Lindenhurst, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - Plumbers Union - Bohemia, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - Building & Construction Trades Council of Nassau & Suffolk Counties Reception, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - Gabe Pressman's Communications Class - New School, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - St. Johns University Alumni Banquet - Hilton, 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - Taxi Drivers with Governor - 55th Street (of 10/21), 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - Mr. Bixby shown with all his secretaries (photos by John Reidy), 1970 October 22 (Box 100)
          - WCBS Radio Station taping of "Lets Find Out", 1970 October 23 (Box 100)
          - Wagner Commission on Local Government Drop-In - 55th Street, 1970 October 23 (Box 100)
          - Endorsement (by?), 1970 October 23 (Box 100)
          - Garment Center Rally, 1970 October 23 (Box 100)
          - Solvay Rally - Onondaga county Reception, 1970 October 23 (Box 100)
          - Queens Walking Tour, 1970 October 24 (Box 100)
          - Spring Valley Shopping Center Tour, 1970 October 24 (Box 100)
          - "Weeklies for Rockefeller" - Pocantico Hills, 1970 October 24 (Box 100)
          - Westchester County Reception, 1970 October 25 (Box 100)
          - Puerto Rican Hometown Mayors Breakfast, 1970 October 26 (Box 100)
          - Ministeria Interfaith Association MTG (M.I.A.), 1970 October 26 (Box 100)
          - Business Leaders Dinner, 1970 October 26 (Box 100)
          - Brookhaven Republican Women's Club Cocktail Party, 1970 October 26 (Box 100)
          - Suffolk County Headquarters Visit & Rally, 1970 October 26 (Box 100)
          - Internal Revenue Service Building Groundbreaking - (Islip), 1970 October 26 (Box 100)
          - Wall Street Rally, 1970 October 27 (Box 100)
          - Jack Kemp Dinner - (testimonial) - Buffalo, 1970 October 27 (Box 100)
          - Erie county Reception - Hamburg, 1970 October 27 (Box 100)
          - WPIX-TV Debate - Tree Gubernatorial Candidates, 1970 October 28 (Box 100)
          - Queens County Annual Republican Committee Rally, 1970 October 28 (Box 100)
          - Mr. Bixby & Group watch TV debates on TV at Campaign Headquarters (photos by John Reidy), 1970 October 28 (Box 100)
          - David Merrick Endorses Governor, 1970 October 29 (Box 100)
          - Rabbis Endorse Governor, 1970 October 29 (Box 100)
          - Queen Walking Tour, 1970 October 29 (Box 100)
          - Nassau County Rally, 1970 October 29 (Box 100)
          - Photos of Campaign Staff People (John Reidy), 1970 October 29 (Box 100)
          - WORK-TV Studio - Rochester (Channel 13 News conference taping), 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
          - Senior Citizens Apartments (Seneca Towers) - Rochester, 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
          - U.D.C. construction of Lincoln National Bank Towers - Syracuse, 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
          - Watertown Press Conference, 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
          - Walking Tour on South Salina Street - Syracuse, 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
          - Airport Press Conference - Watertown, 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
          - Photos of Campaign Staff People (John Reidy), 1970 October 30 (Box 100)
        - 1970 November
          - Governor w/David Merrick, 1970 November 1 (Box 100)
          - NBC-TV Debate - "Direct Line", 1970 November 1 (Box 100)
          - WCBS-TV Debate, 1970 November 1 (Box 100)
          - Breakfast at Ratners Dairy Restaurant - Manhattan, 1970 November 2 (Box 100)
          - Buffalo Campaign Round- Up, 1970 November 2 (Box 100)
          - White Plains Airport Rally, 1970 November 2 (Box 100)
          - Governor & Mrs. Rockefeller vote at Pocantico Hills School, 1970 November 3 (Box 100)
          - New York Republican Club Headquarters Visit, 1970 November 3 (Box 100)
          - Election Night: Victory Celebration at the Roosevelt Hotel (photos by Bob Wands & John Reidy), 1970 November 3 (Box 100)
          - Camel Driver presents flower-covered camel to Mr. Bixby (John Reidy), 1970 November 3 (Box 100)
          - Photos of Campaign Staff Members (John Reidy), 1970 November 3 (Box 100)
      - 1971
        - 1971 January
          - 1971 January 1 (Box 101)
          - 1971 January 6 (Box 101)
          - 1971 January 13 (Box 101)
          - 1971 January 18 (Box 101)
          - 1971 January 22 (Box 101)
        - 1971 March
          - 1971 March 12 (Box 101)
          - 1971 March 16 (Box 101)
        - 1971 April
          - 1971 April 8 (Box 101)
          - 1971 April 15 (Box 101)
          - 1971 April 16 (Box 101)
          - 1971 April 19 (Box 101)
          - 1971 April 26 (Box 101)
        - 1971 May
          - 1971 May 7 (Box 101)
          - 1971 May 13 (Box 101)
          - 1971 May 14 (Box 101)
          - 1971 May 28 (Box 101)
        - 1971 June
          - 1971 June 2 (Box 101)
          - 1971 June 10 (Box 101)
          - 1971 June 17 (Box 101)
          - 1971 June 18 (Box 101)
          - 1971 June 21 (Box 101)
          - 1971 June 25 (Box 101)
        - 1971 July
          - 1971 July 2 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 6 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 7 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 8 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 12 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 15 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 21 (Box 101)
          - 1971 July 27 (Box 101)
        - 1971 August
          - 1971 August 2 (Box 101)
          - 1971 August 19 (Box 101)
          - 1971 August 20 (Box 101)
        - 1971 September
          - 1971 September 15 (Box 101)
          - 1971 September 16 (Box 101)
          - 1971 September 21 (Box 101)
          - 1971 September 27 (Box 101)
          - 1971 September 29 (Box 101)
          - 1971 September 30 (Box 101)
        - 1971 October
          - 1971 October 1 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 8 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 14 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 15 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 19 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 21 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 26 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 28 (Box 101)
          - 1971 October 29 (Box 101)
        - 1971 November
          - 1971 November 1 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 2 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 3 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 10 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 17 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 20 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 22 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 23 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 24 (Box 101)
          - 1971 November 30 (Box 101)
        - 1971 December
          - 1971 December 2 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 3 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 7 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 10 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 13 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 14 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 20 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 22 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 23 (Box 101)
          - 1971 December 31 (Box 101)
      - 1972
        - 1972 January
          - 1972 January 18 (Box 102)
          - 1972 January 19 (Box 102)
          - 1972 January 23 (Box 102)
          - 1972 January 25 (Box 102)
        - 1972 February
          - 1972 February 17 (Box 102)
        - 1972 March
          - 1972 March 11 (Box 102)
          - 1972 March 20 (Box 102)
        - 1972 April
          - 1972 April 3 (Box 102)
          - 1972 April 14 (Box 102)
          - 1972 April 26 (Box 102)
          - 1972 April 27 (Box 102)
        - 1972 May
          - 1972 May 16 (Box 102)
          - 1972 May 22 (Box 102)
          - 1972 May 25 (Box 102)
          - 1972 May 26 (Box 102)
          - 1972 May 30 (Box 102)
          - 1972 May 31 (Box 102)
        - 1972 June
          - 1972 June 8 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 10 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 13 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 14 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 17 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 18 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 19 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 20 (Box 102)
          - 1972 June 22 (Box 102)
        - 1972 July
          - 1972 July 10 (Box 102)
          - 1972 July 24 (Box 102)
          - 1972 July 25 (Box 102)
          - 1972 July 26 (Box 102)
        - 1972 August
          - 1972 August 14 (Box 102)
          - 1972 August 15 (Box 102)
          - 1972 August 17 (Box 102)
        - 1972 September
          - 1972 September 7 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 14 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 15 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 16 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 19 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 20 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 25 (Box 102)
          - 1972 September 28 (Box 102)
        - 1972 October
          - 1972 October 2 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 3 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 4 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 9 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 10 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 11 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 12 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 16 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 19 (Box 102)
          - 1972 October 23 (Box 102)
        - 1972 December
          - 1972 December 6 (Box 102)
          - 1972 December 11 (Box 102)
          - 1972 December 18 (Box 102)
          - 1972 December 19 (Box 102)
      - 1973